Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh.
The simple answer is nonsense.
I know it's your way.
I say no, I'm Team.
I'm so proud of you.
I want you to be a person.
Thank you.
St.
Saturn of the Five Elders
has made landfall. What?
But when did he come ashore?
Yeah, and how?
Everyone but the vice and rear
admirals retreat from the town center?
and hurry!
Retreat from beholding his holy visit.
Something's happening and
they're not telling us.
Even the admirals don't dare
to question a celestial dragon.
He's not just a celestial dragon.
The elder stands above all.
Why did he come all the
way here from Marie-Joan?
I've only seen the elders
in portraits before.
What's going on over there?
What is that lightning?
Bonnie!
What have you done?
T.
Saturn, this is a grave offense.
You've turned your blade against
the highest authority in the world.
Everyone, prepare to strike!
This is bad.
We need to run.
Bonnie, run away!
You destroyed our lives!
Stand back, Incest.
If I didn't want to get stabbed,
then I would have dodged.
Bonnie!
How dare you, you monster!
Episode.
Sanchi!
A wasted effort.
Whoa!
All the blood disappeared!
Seize Dr.
Vegapunk and the others immediately
Wait, you worthless fools?
They're no threat, and
they have nowhere to run.
Stand at the ready! Yes, sir!
And Kizaru, I expected
you to settle this matter.
What happened?
I'm afraid i have no excuse!
only my deep regrets.
and to make matters worse,?
I don't think I can get up.
As for you...
Don't touch him!
Strong run!
Well, I see some pirates
know how to cooperate.
You're a big shot now, Luffy!
Even the world rulers wants your head!
Straw Hat, Luffy.
Jewelry Bonnie.
Your appearance here was
unexpected and unwelcome.
But you've sealed your fate,
and you are surrounded.
If you think you can't escape,
I'd be curious to see how...
Vegapunk.
It's a pity you betrayed us.
You've made many
contributions to the Navy.
I'm grateful for your service.
Who should I kill first?
Name them in order of who
you will create the most.
I want you to die regretting your
rebellion with every ounce of your pain.
Why are humans never content?
Why must they crutch at the forbidden?
Bonnie! No!
What's happening? Hey!
Can anybody else move? Not me!
And it ain't from lack of trying.
It's like I'm being held down.
What is this force?
Even with all my power,
I can't seem to budge.
It must be a Devil Fruit.
Science can't explain this. Oh no! What?
I know the truth.
That you murdered my father.
You bastard!
Ah, Kuma.
Did you also know he was
born into a slave caste?
He was the descendant of a clan
that committed a grave crime.
The sole survivor of the Buccaneer people.
Bonnie.
Ever since I was young, I've had a dream.
I've always wanted to be a hero.
Someone who could save the downtrodden
and free people from suffering?
A warrior of liberation, just like Nika!
Aim for her head!
Prepare to fire!
Bonnie! No!
Don't do this!
Don't shoot!
She's only a child!
If he's a hero, does that mean
he'll come and free me too?
Of course he will.
It's a boy!
Congratulations!
We're so glad you're here with
us. Hello, Kuma. It's Mommy.
Doctor, one last thing.
I assume it's about his blood.
Please don't worry about it.
It will be our little secret.
How is he? Perfect. Welcome back.
Hey, you want to fly?
Off you go.
He sure looks happy.
You need to run, Clep! Hurry!
The government's men are on the island!
They came to the hospital!
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
Wait I'm the only one of
us here who has buccaneer
blood my wife doesn't let
her and my son go Please
have mercy I'm the one you
came here for not them don't
do this just take me and
let my Let your family go!
Kuma.
Don't you worry, okay?
We'll make it through.
I know it.
See that, even at a young
age, he's quite strong.
That's a buccaneer's sleigh for you!
Hey!
There's no time to rest!
Yes, sir.
Do your job right!
Why are you always so slow?
I'm sorry!
Stop hitting me!
Don't cry!
Don't make me kill you!
Hey, Kuma.
Dad, it's you.
You're all beat up. I'm fine.
Really, it's just a few bruises.
But you've grown up so much.
I hope you've been okay, too.
Uh, my master has been
pretty nice to me, actually,
so I guess you could say I'm lucky.
Kuma, the truth is, your mother,
I'm afraid that she's dead.
Well, that means she's in heaven now.
It's better that way.
Trust me.
You'll be okay, Kuro.
You're strong.
You just have to survive.
Don't give up. Why?
I think I'd be better off dead, too.
The Warrior of Liberation will
save you. Have faith. He'll come.
Who is that?
Nika, the sun god, is a hero.
Buccaneers have told tales
of him for generations.
Nika's a part of our heritage.
He'll show up and deliver
us all to freedom one day.
He'll take you to the sea
beneath the free skies.
Are you sure? Of course.
He's no joke.
But Nika is always laughing.
And he makes people
smile with this rhythm.
Quiet you worms!
The moment has finally arrived!
It's time for a triennial game.
the local hunting
Gordportation!
This year's test of
strength and skill is in
a land unaffiliated with
the world government?
Gordbelly!
Its name may be in poor taste!
But the island does possess?
An abundance of natural resources.
Worthy of the divine!
So the first step is to hold?
Our customary human hunt.
And when we're done, the government
will seize the whole island!
This is absurd!
You're going to slaughter
my people for sport?
Are you insane?
This country belongs to us
alone! Your Majesty! How rude!
I don't like that man one bit!
Your majesty now hold on
now this is no good at all.
Saint Garling that was
a false start you've
already taken down the
king of the locals before.
We've even begun your
majesty Saint Garling
is a top contender but he has to start
with Negative 10 000 points the handicap
will just make things more interesting.
Oh, so dashing!
Quite the large deficit.
Satisfactory indeed.
One last note before we start.
In addition to the local rabbits,
we've also assembled a wide selection.
of problematic slaves and
criminals for you to hunt today.
Look at the bars. Unreal.
He's a monster.
One of the slaves escaped.
Hey, wait a minute! You there!
Why the hell didn't you stop him? I...
I'm very sorry, sir.
Then take responsibility
and go hunt him down!
There he is!
Saint Saturn!
We were able to recapture
the escaped slave.
It was the buccaneer child, sir.
Look, kid, you can't just
run away on your own.
We're supposed to be
responsible for each other.
If you get away, all ten of the
guys in our group will be killed.
Hee-haw!
Hey, you!
Hold it right there.
I've seen you.
You're the star of the show.
The fucking ear boy, right? What?
Wow, look at you.
You're huge.
They weren't lying when they
said you've got giant's blood.
My bro here's pretty gigantic himself.
I've just got a big head.
Wait a second.
You got me.
You all look so miserable.
Why don't you try enjoying
life for a change?
We've got a great plan.
So stick with us and you'll see.
I choose life, baby.
What do you say?
Are you with me?
Now today's prey has been
released onto the field.
The 13 super rare rabbits we introduced
are worth 10,000 points each.
There are also 150 rare rabbits.
One hit kills earn you an excellent bonus.
And the champion will receive
these priceless treasures.
Watch and learn, children.
Don't get too cocky-garling.
The man-liars are gonna nab that trophy.
Patience, everyone.
Let's follow the rules.
How could you do this, you monsters?
This is a nightmare!
We're human beings,
not toys, you bastards!
My baby!
We're gonna find a way to
pull this off, no matter what.
Get ready, Kuma.
Okay.
There are 200 world noble hunters!
You have one hour to find
a hoe to hide in, rabbits!
Now run!
God, Valley!
Why are you gonna make me
trek all the way out there?
You know I can't tell you.
Just help me, Garp!
We haven't confirmed the details, but
we can't take any chances with this.
I don't want to get involved
in some world noble field trip.
Just because they poked the hornet's
nest doesn't mean we should.
I warned you, you can't steal treasure
from Pirate Island and get away with it.
They'll get it back for sure.
I wonder, who leaked the intel?
You've got plenty of eyes on the place.
What are you sweating for?
We were expecting some trouble, but we
never thought that Roger would get involved.
I should have led with that!
I'm going!
The Rock Pirates have set sail!
Damn it!
Those bastards got ahead of us!
We gotta catch up! Hurry!
No pirate worth his salt would miss this!
Without further ado, let the games begin!
Die!
Look at that!
Over there, on the coast!
The Navy's got the
whole island surrounded!
It's an entire fleet!
You see?
They've made sure no one
can escape from this place!
And if we can't get out and tell
the world what they've done here,
then they can erase their
crimes from history!
They're planning to kill the locals and
steal the island's natural resources!
And three weeks from
today when their little
murder game is over every
last one of the hundred
thousand rabbits will be
dead don't you understand
before we even realized
it we've gone to hell
Yeah but we just got to survive
three weeks if we can pull
that off we'll be free they're
never going to let you go they've
done this before there are no
survivors from any game wait
what if they're just gonna kill
us all why would they give us
hope Because if you have hope
you'll run for your lives they
don't want to kill people who
know that they'll die that's no
fun for them you can't survive
playing by their rules this
sick game is rigged against us
so we have to turn it on its head
St.
Garling has earned a
whopping 100,000 points!
He must be aiming for high-score rabbits!
Yes, it's off!
Nice jaws, pal.
Good to have a sharkfish man.
Uh, thank you.
Not used to feel comfortable anyway.
This doesn't make sense.
They got the information.
I made sure of that.
But neither the pirates nor the Navy have
done a thing why not I don't understand.
What are you doing?
What I do best?
Manipulating intel!
There's just one ticket out of here!
the prizes for the game!
the prizes?
One is a Devil Fruit
with mythical strength.
It lets you transform into an azure
dragon They've got another one to a
Devil Fruit that gives you the power to
send people flying to faraway islands
It's called the pawpaw fruit.
If we can eat one of those
fruits, we'll have it made.
We'll track them down, soar over the
blockade, and leave this hellhole in the dust.
There's no way, though.
The prizes are at the
center of the island.
Soon as they spot us,
we're done for. Don't fret.
I'm a thief and a pro at wiretapping.
Two weeks ago, I leaked some intel
about this island to the outside.
That means pirates will be
flooding this place soon.
They'll want that sweet treasure.
It's gonna be pandemonium!
Thing is, that alone won't be
enough to pull off our plan.
One of us will have to serve as a decoy.
We gotta distract the
Celestial Dragons to rob them.
A decoy?
I'll do it.
Kuma!
I'm big and tough, so I think I
can survive longer than the others.
Besides, I don't want
to see anyone else hide.
Yee-haw!
Ah!
Now we're talking Kuma, and
I won't let you die either.
Let's escape God Valley, together!
Oh! What the hell?
They're coming from the east!
It's the Rocks Pirates!
The Rocks Pirates? But why?
Wait, there are others too!
It's a whole swarm of infamous pirates.
There was no alert.
How could this happen?
Fire, now!
Don't bother, you Navy dogs.
Rocks Pirates, follow me!
What was that, Rocks?
You think you can order
me around? Go to hell!
Oh, stop it, Newgate.
Don't do this now.
Planning to do something today, Stussy?
You're one to talk, Gloriosa.
It's finders' keep, as I say.
We good with that?
You won't get a thing.
I'll be taking both fruits.
Come on, Lin-Man, you can't even use them.
They're my treasure, mate.
Rox is a damn fool.
He'll forget why we're even here.
Let's run in and check the treasure.
Stop talking like you are
a leader, you hypocrite!
I'm about to wreck this whole island.
Get your head out of the clouds
and quit trying to act tough.
Let's grab the treasure
and take to the sea.
I heard that Roger
might be showing up too.
I'll take him on.
What did I just say, you brat?
This fight will decide it all.
That's what we want, all of us.
Then let's settle this.
The rocks pirates have made landfall.
Pirates here!
What are you defense doing?
If anything happens to
us, we'll see you dead.
Reporting in!
Dangerous pirates are
coming from all directions.
We can't stop them.
How did they know?
This event was strictly confidential.
Their current objective is unclear.
Incoming!
On the western shore.
That's the Roger pirates.
In a whole year, you have any idea
how much I've been stewing on this?
Gonna be a wild one.
Roger, no calling first dibs!
Just because you're the captain.
Yeah, let's go.
Pull back the marines.
Protect the celestial dragons.
So pathetic!
What was the point of the blockade?
Holy nights to battle!
All right.
Roger and rocks.
I don't think we should
hold out A
piece
of Roger
Is this a Devil Fruit?
Yeah.
Got no idea which is which, though.
Just eat.
There you are.
That was close, huh?
Eva, are you all right?
Now for my other treasure.
Quick, eat it!
You better fork that over
now, you little shit.
Don't think twice.
Eat that fruit and survive, Kuma!
Only one of us has to live!
A single survivor means we win!
You did it!
Run, Kuma, run!
Listen to me, buccaneer boy.
You will live as a
slave, then you will die.
That is your lot in life.
Your fate has been decided
by the course of history.
He's someone important.
He says some people are born to rule.
That's not right.
Some people are born to be slaves.
Why are we born at all?
I don't know much.
But if I really do have some
power, Then I want to be like Mock.
I want to protect people from suffering.
I want to free as many slaves as I can.
This is why.
Your people need to be eliminated!
Get back here, rocks.
Out of my way, Roger!
This incident would fade into
the dark shadows of history.
They wrote about Garp's heroics,
but didn't mention anything
else that happened that day.
The people in power
write our history for us.
This reporter Morgans
is nothing but a hack!
We were there, and we might
never learn the truth.
All we can do is hope and pray.
How long are you going to
keep doing that, by the way?
I'm praying.
For all the lives that
I wasn't able to save.
Would you cut it out?
You did pretty damn good.
Even in all that chaos,
you saved 500 people.
He's right, Kumaji.
You were awesome.
They were all so grateful that they cried.
And that I cried too.
But I never forget.
Those hands can do more than pray.
They're the hands of liberation.
Liberation?
Really?
You just have to survive.
Don't give up.
The warrior of liberation will save you.
So your family ran a church
when you were born, huh?
Well, that would explain
why you turned out this way.
Ha!
So long, pals!
I'm heading out to sea!
I'm free now, so I gotta enjoy it!
I hope we meet again.
I'll never forget your face.
Actually, I get that one a lot.
Big bro, I still gotta figure out my life.
I'll stay with Kumachi.
Good luck.
Farewell, my darling compatriots.
All right.
I'm the eldest here by four years.
So that means it's my job to keep you fed.
You can do it, kumachi!
Looking good!
Let's sell them!
No more scavenging.
No stealing.
We'll work for our food, honest-like.
Now let's head off to market. Yeah!
We sold it all!
I worked up an appetite.
What do you want to eat today?
I'll be fine with anything.
You can pick. Yay!
Dadan?
Never seen you two around.
Who are you?
You sure are huge.
How old are you?
I'm big, but I'm nine.
You're joking! No way!
You're a liar!
Big monster!
I'm sorry, we got off to a bad start.
Jimmy is usually nice.
What?
The bump's gone.
It doesn't hurt anymore. It's magic!
That was so cool, Kumachi!
You're awesome!
Kumanshee!
Kumanshee! Kumanshee!
Alright, let's eat.
Don't gotta tell me!
I want more! Here. Are you sure?
So yummy!
It's okay if you want to eat a
lot, but we'll have to work hard.
Okay!
By the way, what age
did you become a slave?
When I was four.
Same as me!
Don't know if that's something
for you to smile about.
I'm four.
I'm four. Hmm? Ginny?
Come on, Ginny!
It was so bright.
It's coming here!
I'm so happy.
I have wanted to.
I don't even know
what it meant.
I don't want anyone else.
I don't wanna be able...
I'm not leaving.
It won't be me anymore.
I got your hands on my hand.
I can't eat the sky,
but the deep sea will light up.
We are every day, we are not every day.
We are not here, we are here.
I don't think that's what I'm saying.